<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>

	  <item>
		<title>Dota 2: Asia Championships</title>
		<link>http://www.dota2.com.cn/dac/english/match</link>
		<description>
			The Dota 2 Asia Championships group stage finished with Empire and OG taking the helm for the western teams entering the upper bracket, while Newbee and Invictus Gaming are the two Chinese representatives. The main event will feature a double elimination bracket, and the winners of each group will battle it out for a chance to land a place at the lan finals. OG and Newbee are kicking things off in the upper bracket today at 18:00 PDT / 03:00 CEST, while LGD.Forever Young will tackle iG Vitality in the lower bracket tomorrow at 02:00 PDT / 11:00 CEST.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Overwatch: APEX Season 2</title>
		<link>https://www.twitch.tv/ognglobal</link>
		<description>
			Lunatic-Hai faced Meta Athena on Tuesday during a tense semifinal match which saw the previous runner-up’s take Athena down for their third chance to win a major championship. Lunatic-Hai obliterated Athena on both Nepal and Eichenwalde, and they continuously punished their over-aggressive plays with decisive payload pushes. Lunatic-Hai will now face RunAway in the APEX finals on April 8th, but the APEX action doesn’t stop there as Meta Athena will take on LW Blue to contest the bronze title.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Overwatch: PIT Championship</title>
		<link>http://overwatchpit.com/schedule/</link>
		<description>
			The best Overwatch teams from Europe and North America have been busy fighting it out for their chance to claim the PIT title and their share of a $15,000 prize pool. Ninja’s in Pyjamas and Misfits are currently at the top of the European bracket, but this could soon change. SNG Ninjas and Movistar Riders are kicking this weekend’s action off today at 09:00 PDT / 18:00 CEST, while the North American branch will see Rise take on LG Evil later at 16:00 PDT / 01:00 CEST.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Rocket League: Championship Series</title>
		<link>http://rlcs.gg/article/rlcs-season-3-league-play-schedule</link>
		<description>
			Week three of the Rocket League Championship: Series is underway this weekend when NRG take on Denial Esports this Saturday at 12:00 PDT / 21:00 CEST. So far Selfless look to be the team to beat as they recently qualified for the playoffs with four wins. If Selfless can beat Atelier and G2 Esports this weekend, they can easily hang on to the top spot in North America. Meanwhile, European team Pocket Aces now sit at the top of the leaderboard after beating both Penta and Cow Nose in week two. The previous European leaders The Leftovers will be looking for a decisive win when they tackle Penta this Sunday.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Tickets for The International 2017</title>
		<link>http://www.ticketmaster.com/The-International-Dota-2-Championship-tickets/artist/1982004</link>
		<description>
			The International Dota 2 Championship returns to Seattle's KeyArena from Monday, August 7th through Saturday, August 12th, once again gathering the world’s top Dota teams together to vie for the Aegis of Champions.Tickets will go on sale Tuesday, April 4th at 10:00 AM and 10:00 PM PDT, with two ticket types available. The Midweek ticket—available for $100—will grant attendance to the first four days of the event, August 7th – 10th. The Finals ticket—available for $200—will grant access to the last two days, August 11th and 12th.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Dota 2 launches revamped Jakiro</title>
		<link>https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/2017/03/16/with-ice-and-fire-dota-2-launches-revamped-jakiro</link>
		<description>
			Jakiro from Dota 2, once thought to be the world’s most popular flying plastic bag since that one in American Beauty, has been revealed as a two-headed dragon. Valve yesterday pumped out a Dota 2 update which included the long-promised new model for the support character(s), which makes clear that Jakiro are actually a dragon and not a burst bin bag. Who knew! The new Jakiro mostly follows the same concept, though Blue Head’s cute beard o’ barbels has become a jawline so stern even Judge Dredd would envy it.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Bladeform Legacy Update</title>
		<link>https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=http://www.dota2.com/bladeformlegacy</link>
		<description>
			Today, the mask is unveiled. Juggernaut's Arcana is now available. Featuring a custom Dragon Spirit ancestor and all-new animations and effects, the Bladeform Legacy marks a new chapter for the wandering warrior from the Isle of Masks.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>CS:GO: StarLadder i-League Season 3</title>
		<link>https://starladder.com/en/csgostarseries-s3/matches</link>
		<description>
			The best American and European teams will clash for their chance to secure a place in the LAN finals of the StarSeries, and with potential $300,000 at stake, only the top two teams from each bracket will secure tickets to the finals, held in Kiev, Ukraine. Matches will be played in a best-of-three single elimination, which will heighten the pressure and leave little room for error. OpTic Gaming and Eanix are kicking things off in America today at 17:30 PST / 02:30 CET, while the European games kick off Saturday with Team EnVyUs vs. BIG at 07:00 PST / 16:00 CET.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Dota 2: Kiev Major Regional Qualifiers</title>
		<link>https://www.dotabuff.com/esports/leagues/5316</link>
		<description>
			The Kiev Major qualifiers have been taking place all around the world and the best teams will be fighting it out in the regional qualifiers today. In Europe, Elements Pro Gaming, Team Secret, Ninjas in Pyjamas, B)ears, ALTERNATE aTTaX, Cloud9 and Alliance will battle it out. Elements Pro Gaming and ALTERNATE aTTaX are kicking things off at today at 04:30 PST / 13:30 CET, but the action doesn’t stop there as various matches will be played throughout the day.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>League of Legends: 2017 EU LCS Spring Split</title>
		<link>http://www.lolesports.com/en_US/eu-lcs/eu_2017_spring/schedule/default</link>
		<description>
			The Giants had another tough week and they desperately tried to climb up from the bottom rankings, but G2 and Fnatic crushed their hopes of making it to this year's playoffs. Meanwhile, Roccat managed to surprise everyone with their 2-0 victory over Misfits, which has given the team a chance to rival Fnatic for third place. Vitality on the other hand continued to prove that they are one of the most inconsistent teams in the EU LCS. They played extremely passive against Splyce, which resulted in two games with a lot of one-sided action. Vitality looked like a completely different team when they played their second series against H2k. Game one went in H2K's favour, but Vitality's managed to come back in game two by creating pressure around the map. However, a Baron throw saw H2K steal away game three and they broke open Vitality's Nexus after a very close performance.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>League of Legends: 2017 NA LCS Spring Split</title>
		<link>http://www.lolesports.com/en_US/na-lcs/na_2017_spring/schedule/default</link>
		<description>
			Cloud9’s series against Dignitas was a close one, but a clutch teamfight and major plays from Jensen’s Orianna gave C9 the power they need to dominate Dignitas. Phoenix1 were next on C9’s hit list and they proved critics wrong when they beat P1 2-0, which landed them with a place in this year’s playoffs. Meanwhile, Dignitas managed grab their playoff spot by eliminating Immortals, and they’ll be looking to secure another decisive win against Phoenix1.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>League of Legends: 2017 NA LCS Spring Split 2</title>
		<link>http://www.lolesports.com/en_US/na-lcs/na_2017_spring/schedule/default</link>
		<description>
			Meanwhile, Team Liquid tried to avoid relegation in week nine by picking up two victories against TSM and FlyQuest. Team Liquid’s managed to beat TSM after DoubleLift’s Ezreal obliterated TSM’s bot-lane and carried his team to victory. However, FlyQuest’s Hai managed to stop them dead in their tracks with his Talon plays, and he secured a playoffs spot for FlyQuest and a promotion tournament spot for Team Liquid.
		</description>
	  </item>
	 
	  <item>
		<title>Hearthstone: 2017 HCT Asia-Pacific Winter Playoffs</title>
		<link>http://eu.battle.net/hearthstone/en/esports/schedule/</link>
		<description>
			Last weekend the Americas branch of the Hearthstone Championship determined which four players (DrJikininki, DocPwn, Tarei and Fr0zen) will be competing at the Hearthstone Winter Championship in the Bahamas. This weekend we’ll see which players have what it takes to represent Asia and be crowned the HCT Asia-Pacific Winter Champion. The matches kick off today at 18:00 PST / 03:00 CET, and continue the same time Sunday.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	  <item>
		<title>Smite: SPL 2017</title>
		<link>http://esports.smitegame.com/matchset/february-25-2017-nrg-esports-vs-elevate/</link>
		<description>
			The second week of the SPL will continue this Saturday where Elevate and NRG eSports will clash. Obey Alliance delivered a shocking blow to NRG when they beat them 2-0, but NRG will be hoping to put this loss behind them and beat Elevate this weekend. The last time NRG lost a set was to Paradigm at the Super Regionals in 2015, so the upcoming clash will certainly be interesting and could go either way. Make sure you tune into action at 10:00 PST / 19:00 CET.
		</description>
	  </item>

	  <item>
		<title>Amit Viva7</title>
		<link>http://esports.smitegame.com/matchset/february-25-2017-nrg-esports-vs-elevate/</link>
		<description>
			Muthuraj sir took viva.
		</description>
	  </item>
	  
	</channel>

</rss>
